{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750375088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750375088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750383587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750383587"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750409147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750409147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750415186","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750415186"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750426370","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750426370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_f-t-m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750434565","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750434565"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_f-t-m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750443721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750443721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_w-b-m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750448062","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750448062"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-a-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750451645","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750451645"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750456959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750456959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750460542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750460542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_h-v-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750465900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750465900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_h-v-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750470140","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750470140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-t-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750475387","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750475387"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-t-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750478765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750478764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-l-u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750482261","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750482261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750487747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750487747"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750491577","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750491576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-o-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750496807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750496807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-o-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750500091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750500091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-v-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750505473","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750505473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-v-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750511283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750511281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7a3bd1fb-1444-4fee-bc96-c6ee6c6d5872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-v-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750526821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750526821"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-l-u"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750532489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750532489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-l-u"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750535552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750535552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-a-m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750540909","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750540909"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-a-m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750544005","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750544005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_h-v-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750549304","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750549304"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_h-v-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750553151","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750553151"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750558452","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750558452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750562231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750562231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_f-t-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750568197","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750568197"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_f-t-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750571916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750571916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750577065","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750577065"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750580429","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750580429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f3bb4ee4-6574-46b4-a275-e6e1a6d1113c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750590901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750590900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750591635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750591634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750591876","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750591875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750592586","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750592585"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750593577","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750593575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750594388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750594386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750594688","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750594688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750595719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750595719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750598522","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750598521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750599523","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750599522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750600319","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750600319"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750600836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750600835"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750601765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750601764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750602414","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750602413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750603117","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750603116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750603938","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750603938"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750606374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750606373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750606789","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750606788"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750607564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750607563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750608753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750608753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750609192","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750609191"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750610252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750610251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750613491","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750613490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750614339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750614339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750615489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750615489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750618032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750618031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750618372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750618371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750619092","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750619091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750620253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750620253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750620481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750620480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750620695","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750620695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750621591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750621589"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750623886","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750623886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750624773","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750624772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750627811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750627809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750628824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750628823"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750629595","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750629595"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750630186","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750630185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750631612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750631611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" ANAPOITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750632637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750632636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750633027","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750633027"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750633293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750633293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750633418","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750633417"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750634812","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750634812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750636020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750636019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750637189","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750637188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750638132","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750638131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750640331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750640330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750641146","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750641146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750641620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750641620"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750642314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750642314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750643047","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750643047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750644090","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750644090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750645214","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750645214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750646059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750646059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750646193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750646193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750646988","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750646988"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750647574","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750647573"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750648208","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750648208"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750649910","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750649909"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" HUNGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750650558","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750650558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750651332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750651331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750652584","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750652583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750653898","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750653897"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750655179","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750655178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750655228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750655228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750662023","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750662023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750667648","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750667647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750672913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750672913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" e37825e0-2e27-4e8d-a6fa-5b693f4f8ff7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750686406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750686405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unanguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750688037","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750688037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unanguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNANGURUMA"," userResponse":" UNANGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750691319","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750691319"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNANGURUMA"," userResponse":" UNANGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750691999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750691998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" KUPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750692614","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750692614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAO"," userResponse":" MAKAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750692908","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750692908"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750693372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750693372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750694125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750694123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unanguruma kupita makao yetu kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750697307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750697307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ni mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750697516","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750697516"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ni mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750698347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750698347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ni mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750702020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750702019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKIBANDUA"," userResponse":" UNAKIBANDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750702618","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750702617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750703249","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750703248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750704088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750704086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750704754","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750704754"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONONI"," userResponse":" MKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750705266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750705265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibandua kishada changu kutoka mkononi mwangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750709220","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750709220"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAKIFUATA"," userResponse":" NINAKIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750709822","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750709821"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750710463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750710462"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750711127","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750711126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750711657","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750711657"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750712392","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750712392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750713497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750713496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNANIRUSHA"," userResponse":" UNANIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750714198","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750714198"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750714767","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750714766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakifuata kishada changu lakini Upepo mkali unanirusha mbali nacho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NACHO"," userResponse":" NACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750717852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750717851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unageuka na kuwa dhoruba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750719008","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750719006"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unageuka na kuwa dhoruba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAGEUKA"," userResponse":" UNAGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750719507","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750719506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unageuka na kuwa dhoruba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750720158","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750720157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unageuka na kuwa dhoruba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750721148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750721147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo unageuka na kuwa dhoruba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750724242","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750724242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKIBEBA"," userResponse":" UNAKIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750724862","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750724862"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750725492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750725491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750726262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750726261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750727313","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750727312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750727575","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750727574"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750728660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750728659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakibeba kishada changu juu zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750731997","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750731997"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750732714","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750732713"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750732816","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750732816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750733824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750733824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTISHA"," userResponse":" KUTISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750735455","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750735454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANIMEZA"," userResponse":" INANIMEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750736208","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750736208"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIMA"," userResponse":" MZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750736917","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750736916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dhoruba hii ya kutisha inanimeza mzima mzima!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIMA"," userResponse":" MZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750739472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750739472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sioni chochote sigusi chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIONI"," userResponse":" SIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750740332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750740331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sioni chochote sigusi chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750741525","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750741525"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sioni chochote sigusi chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIGUSI"," userResponse":" SIGUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750742384","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750742383"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sioni chochote sigusi chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750746108","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750746108"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakumbuka kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" NINAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750746824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750746824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakumbuka kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750747740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750747740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakumbuka kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750749135","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750749134"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninakumbuka kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750751661","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750751660"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je kiko wapi sasa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750752643","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750752643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je kiko wapi sasa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKO"," userResponse":" KIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750753265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750753265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je kiko wapi sasa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750754449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750754448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je kiko wapi sasa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750757025","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750757024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kimenaswa mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750757999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750757998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kimenaswa mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMENASWA"," userResponse":" KIMENASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750758737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750758737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kimenaswa mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750761742","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750761742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda bado kinapeperushwa angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750762439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750762438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda bado kinapeperushwa angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750763144","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750763144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda bado kinapeperushwa angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750764319","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750764319"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda bado kinapeperushwa angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINAPEPERUSHWA"," userResponse":" KINAPEPERUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750765060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750765059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda bado kinapeperushwa angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750768132","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750768131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo huu mkali mwishowe unapungua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750768621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750768621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo huu mkali mwishowe unapungua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750769401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750769400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo huu mkali mwishowe unapungua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750770365","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750770364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo huu mkali mwishowe unapungua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHOWE"," userResponse":" MWISHOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750771011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750771011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo huu mkali mwishowe unapungua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAPUNGUA"," userResponse":" UNAPUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750774817","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750774816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi bado ninazunguka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750775275","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750775275"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi bado ninazunguka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750775846","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750775846"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi bado ninazunguka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750777029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750777029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi bado ninazunguka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAZUNGUKA"," userResponse":" NINAZUNGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750780683","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750780683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAACHA"," userResponse":" NINAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750781727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750781727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZUNGUKA"," userResponse":" KUZUNGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750782182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750782181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750783125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750783124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAZAMA"," userResponse":" KUTAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750783753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750783753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750784417","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750784416"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaacha kuzunguka na kutazama mahali nipo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPO"," userResponse":" NIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750786675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750786675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750787494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750787494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750788314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750788313"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750789056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750789056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750789883","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750789883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEENDA"," userResponse":" UMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750790831","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750790830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je Upepo ule mkali umeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750794432","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750794432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikioni kishada changu kizuri popote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIONI"," userResponse":" SIKIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750795026","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750795026"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikioni kishada changu kizuri popote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750795578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750795578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikioni kishada changu kizuri popote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750796206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750796205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikioni kishada changu kizuri popote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750797270","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750797269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikioni kishada changu kizuri popote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPOTE"," userResponse":" POPOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750800392","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750800392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siusikii tena Upepo mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIUSIKII"," userResponse":" SIUSIKII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750801046","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750801046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siusikii tena Upepo mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750801515","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750801515"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siusikii tena Upepo mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750802469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750802469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siusikii tena Upepo mkali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750805722","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750805721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750806671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750806667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750807915","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750807915"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIPATA"," userResponse":" NITAKIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750808604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750808603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHADA"," userResponse":" KISHADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750809168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750809168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750810049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750810048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda kesho nitakipata kishada changu kizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750813018","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750813018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750813860","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750813859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750814661","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750814661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750815231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750815231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750815659","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750815651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750816466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750816466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750817430","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750817429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750817742","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750817741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750818335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750818335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750820992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750820990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750821073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750821073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750829424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750829424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750839657","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750839656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750845328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750845327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750853318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750853318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750859080","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750859079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750864951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750864950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750869782","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750869781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750878297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750878297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750884185","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750884185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750890056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750890056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750895112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750895111"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750915723","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750915722"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 6d25dab4-7eb5-4fb9-a6c9-f55aeabccff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543750915792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543750915792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b0dbe0ec-8848-4fd0-b8a7-a91c22fa9360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_28"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina lake lina maana ya 'aliye mzuri' katika lugha yake ya Lubukusu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751068652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751068651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b0dbe0ec-8848-4fd0-b8a7-a91c22fa9360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_28"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jina lake lina maana ya 'aliye mzuri' katika lugha yake ya Lubukusu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751068741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751068741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" a179c67a-1ee0-48f8-950a-13f243a2e151"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_28"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda utanipa chungwa mbivu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751079650","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751079649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751081576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751081576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751081703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751081703"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751110630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751110629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751117073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751117072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751135233","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751135233"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 1aaeb235-1048-463b-b0db-5fe72d686d24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751135304","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751135304"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b82b36e5-ad11-4f93-92df-1de454b54a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751149281","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751149281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751151392","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751151392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751153474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751153474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751156629","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751156629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751158840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751158840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751161035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751161035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751163816","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751163816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751163992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751163992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751248959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751248958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751256315","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751256315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" cf535ab9-fcc4-4658-a951-9d71a7c8f225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751267456","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751267456"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751273266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751273266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751274855","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751274855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751279591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751279590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751281165","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751281165"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751284213","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751284213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751285781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751285781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751291474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751291474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751293075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751293075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751296250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751296250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751297821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751297821"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" NANASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751301489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751301489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751303061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751303061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751307126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751307126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751308720","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751308720"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751312211","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751312210"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751313795","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751313795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751313840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751313840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751317152","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751317152"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751319712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751319711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751321293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751321293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751324855","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751324854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751326463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751326463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751329687","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751329687"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751331268","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751331268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751334643","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751334643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751336229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751336229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyumba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751341868","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751341868"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyumba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751343480","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751343479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751348817","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751348816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751350428","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751350428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751352901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751352900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751354490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751354490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751357841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751357841"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751359406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751359406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751369854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751369854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751371491","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751371490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" NZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751374955","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751374954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751376520","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751376520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751381356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751381356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751382920","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751382920"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751386774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751386774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751388818","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751388817"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751389048","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751389048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751394788","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751394787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751401228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751401228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 39352fbb-5e71-4f91-a0c9-717f64ddf23c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751418174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751418174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751421703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751421703"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751426206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751426206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751426805","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751426805"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751433695","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751433695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751440860","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751440860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751449936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751449936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751459022","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751459021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751467765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751467764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751475709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751475709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 9cdaf479-5941-40c3-81b7-0deeadbebca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751489809","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751489809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" 7900b932-2035-4450-9b5d-b00784475e83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751540785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751540785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751572379","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751572379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751616583","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751616583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751643040","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751643040"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751645720","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751645720"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751648391","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751648391"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751651276","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751651276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751684441","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751684441"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751704206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751704205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751704305","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751704305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751710798","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751710798"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751728537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751728536"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751735840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751735840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751742019","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751742018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751758400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751758400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" f97ac068-e7b7-41ba-9889-d993255a2c42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751758495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751758494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" a5a3e873-0ffa-442d-a5b0-d803cc2c1f36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751766694","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751766694"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" a5a3e873-0ffa-442d-a5b0-d803cc2c1f36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751782660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751782660"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751784138","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751784137"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751786252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751786252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751796691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751796691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751803399","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751803398"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751825469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751825469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751842726","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751842726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751851243","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751851243"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751858239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751858238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543751863282","data":{"timestamp":" 1543751863281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_143240"," gameId":" b178fade-e727-4042-acc4-0198a0bc8144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}